My name is Daniel Ejeh. I reside in the Niger state, Nigeria.
This is my wife and these are my children.
They have accused me of being a wizard,
as a result of two of my children who died mysteriously.
Not only that, some of my relatives also accused me.
This is how it happened:
the first one, my son, died.
Secondly, my first daughter died last year.
They have all accused me of killing my children using witchcraft.
They say I should come here to confirm whether I am a wizard or not.
Lord I pray, I want the man to God to help me, to tell the whole world
whether I am a wizard or not, whether I'm the killer of the children or not.
Let the world witness the whole thing.
My wife has not been cooking for me for more than eight years now.
There is nothing like a relationship between husband and wife.
My children have neglected me, mistreated me,
even abused me by saying that I'm a useless father.
I don’t know what to do.
Man of God, kindly come and rescue me from this predicament.
My name is Mrs Agnes Ejeh.
This is my husband; these are my children.
I married this man, we were living happily
until he lost his job. Then he joined a chemist seller (pharmacy).
When he joined the association, everything changed in the house
to the extent that I got sick. I was seriously sick.
They carried me to so many places to confirm what was wrong with me.
Nobody knew the solution. Then they took me home.
From there, they confirmed that my husband
was the one who wanted to kill me,
and that he was the one causing the harm.
After that, my son died without falling sick, he just died like that.
They confirmed that my husband was killing my children using witchcraft.
Four years later, my daughter was cooking in the kitchen and
fire came from nowhere and burnt her.
We took her to Enugu hospital. We were there for two years.
My husband abandoned me and my daughter there.
My husband is responsible for the witchcraft.
We went to many places to confirm – from both herbalists and men of God.
They confirmed that he's a great wizard.
I went to church; they were praying. They told him to stand up and then said,
"You are a great wizard; you killed two of your children."
They told me that he has a python under his bed
and that is what he is using to kill my children.
He denied it.
He said that he didn’t know anything about it.
He abandoned me and my children. I'm the one taking care of their food.
Whether we get food, or not – he doesn’t care about us.
No school, no job – he doesn’t care.
He will never sit down for one day and think about what is happening in my family.
I am Esther Ejeh.
It all started in 2001 when we lost our brother.
After they took him home for the burial we went to a witchdoctor
who confirmed that my father was responsible for the killing.
After four years, there was an incident of which we cannot explain how it happened.
I got burnt and I was taken to the hospital.
I spent close to two years in hospital.
He abandoned me and my mother in the hospital.
So, it was only my mum who was taking care of me for that period in the hospital.
We believe that he is responsible for what happened to me.
Four years later, my elder sister who all the family put their hope in,
died a month after her youth service had ended.
They took her corpse home. After the burial they went to confirm.
They said that my dad was responsible.
I believe that he is a wizard.
My name is Mr Henry Ejeh.
They said that our dad was a wizard and that he was responsible for our elder sister's death.
They even said that I'm the next person in line to die.
They have dreams – seeing me in a coffin.
He's a wizard, sir.
My name is Mr Douglas Ejeh.
My father is a wizard.
It happened like this,
my first brother died, I wasn’t around.
I came back from school, they told me that my brother had died and they had buried him.
Secondly, my sister, suddenly after her National Youth Corps Service,
she just came home and a month later, she died too.
He was responsible for the killing of our brother and sister.
That is why we came here – to confirm if really he is the one.
My name is Miss Comfort Ejeh.
My father is a wizard.
The reason I say so is because I used to be very close to him
but when everything happened, I was so scared and everybody was accusing him.
I believed everything my mum told me and everything I was seeing in the family - that he's a wizard.
I want to ask you a question.
Who is T.B. Joshua?
Before we go into the matter.
A prophet of God.
You are a prophet.
Why do you choose to come here?
To find out whether our dad is a wizard.
I want to join your family.
Will you accept me?
Yes, sir.
I am joining this family.
If I say something now, it will strike your mind.
Every one of us is going on our knees to ask for forgiveness.
What are we asking for forgiveness for?
Because we cannot act with God.
So, we cannot know God's opinion about ourselves and about others.
That is the sin we have committed.
Tell your neighbor; "The sin you have committed -
you cannot act with God".
Once you cannot act with God,
you cannot know God's opinion,
about yourself and about others.
Everyone here has committed the same sin you have committed today.
This man is being judged by his character.
Very, very, very, tough – too tough.
It has now become affliction. He is now being judged by his attitude.
He is not a wizard.
I magnify Your name forever.
You are everlasting God, King of Kings.
Oh God, thank You.
Thank You.
OK, no problem.
OK, don't worry - it is all right.
I will host you people.
There is nothing like a wizard in this man.
So please, let us go on our knees.
One thing you owe God now – forgiveness.
You need to forgive because you need to be forgiven.
Don't count it against your wife or your children, what has happened in the past.
There is nothing to be delivered from, if he is not a wizard.
It is an affliction, that there would a lie against you everywhere.
Man of God, thank you for helping me.
Thank you for uniting my family together.
I pray that God will enlarge your coasts,
that the ministry will grow "from strength to strength" in the name of Jesus.
What is the cause of the death of the two children and the tragedy in the house?
It is true that death is roaming about in the family
and it is true that another person is working towards the death of another person.
What you said is nothing but the truth that there is another person.
There is a spirit of death going round the house.
Ask your father, he will tell you what happened to his brothers in their family.
It is not your father, but there is a spirit of death at certain level.
Because they know these children, they are saviours of the home.
This death is not coming through your father, it is a generational curse -
being inherited.
Remember before you had this fire burn, you fasted a week after the burn.
Yes, sir.
The same day this happened to me, I was so sad throughout the day
that they asked me what was wrong with me but I couldn’t explain.
That was the same day in the night, that this happened to me.
If not that fasting and prayer you did, you would have died.
Now, the home will be delivered.
What you need to do for me now - is to give your father love.
Give your husband love.
After the Sunday service the Ejeh family ate a meal together,
with all of the family seated around the same table happy and content.
The love of God has been restored to this home, as Mr Ejeh lovingly gives his wife a drink,
and smiles being on all of their faces.
Let's hear from them.
We want to thank God for the reconciliation of this family and for a good future ahead -
we want to say, "Cheers!"
In the name of Jesus Christ, the family drinks a toast to their reconciliation, and the bright future ahead.
Thanks to the prophetic revelation of T.B. Joshua that Mr Ejeh is not a wizard,
nor is he responsible for their trouble.
And now that a man of God has also exposed the cause of their problem,
the unity among the family is as if there had never been a problem.
In fact, I am very grateful, very happy.
There is no adjective to describe my joy today!
I really thank God for this unity.
In fact, we are just like a new couple today!
Glory be to God in the name of Jesus.
The sky is my limit. I don’t know how to express the kind of joy,
that is going through my mind.
I just give God the glory for everything.
I feel so excited and happy for the reconciling of my family like this.
To sit at the same table to eat happily, peacefully -
I thank God for what God had done in our lives.
Indeed I am very happy; I am so excited that I can't express what is going through my mind now.
I really thank God for this. This is really a union.
I am very happy; I am very excited; I am full of joy!
I don’t know how to say it, but I really thank God for what He has done.
The right knowledge of God settled peace.
[song] After so many years of my labour, the Lord has given me a joy in my heart. [song]